České titulky Kiriu (2017)
♫ Vzbudil jsem se před půlnocí. Jsem zmatený jak oceán. ♫
♫ Hvězdy zapomněly svítit. ♫
♫ Byli jsme děti. ♫
♫ Byli jsme dětmi narozenými na této lodi. ♫
♫ Most o kterém lidi mluví je jako malá bárka. ♫
♫ Můžeš slyšet šepot přes palubu. ♫
♫ Její vlajka vlaje v deštivé bouři. ♫
♫ Ale nekonečné lidské spory ♫
♫ nás ženou na dvě nejvzdálenější strany ♫
♫ s kacíři, extrémy a zapomenutými sliby .♫
♫ Když tisíce tisíců vrstev barvy ♫
♫ tiše kvetou do konce temné noci? ♫
♫ Nad oblaky je paprsek světla ♫
♫ jako koruna.  ♫
Magická hvězda
~ Epizoda 3 ~
Emperor, I have picked some days for the wedding.
Emperor, please pick a good date to marry the consort as soon as possible.
Let me think about it more. This doesn't need to be resolved immediately.
It's better that Your Majesty choose one soon. The convoy sent by the Helan King of the Great Plains
- most likely have entered our borders already. Very soon, they will reach the capital.- This...
Emperor!
What is happening Eunuch Cao?
I just received a message
Something bad happened to the wedding convoy sent by the King of Helan.
What happened?
It was said that when they stopped at Yanjiao Town to rest and reorganize,
they joined the temple festival in the area and an accident happened.
Princess Gu Li...was burnt to death.
Speak clearly. Why would they join the temple festival there?
Even if they joined, why would a normal person be burnt to death?
Unfortunately, there was only this in report.
The details are not confirmed yet.
When something like this suddenly happens,
it makes me really sad.
However, one cannot come back from the dead.
Come, send my message, and give Princess Gu Li
as Royal Consort and send men to Helan Country to extend our condolences.
Emperor, this happened so suddenly that something must be wrong. We should figure out what happened first.
Hey, Minister Ding.
Many things happen in life. It is decided whether your life is short or long.
We should not bother her and let her rest in peace.
I hope that this is only a coincidence.
This better have nothing to do with Bai Ze.
This is definitely not a coincidence. What does Bai Ze want to do?
A Ji Ya, let the past be the past.
From today onwards, you are free.
You won't have to deal with other's demands and serve them.
Exactly.
Wow, can you guys smell this awesome fragrance?
This is my best noodle dish. Hurry and get it a try.
Lady, this is my best, best dish.
No, no, noodles.
After you eat it, you will be able to forget
- everything that was unhappy.  - It's only a bowl of noodles.
It's not a drink that makes you forget everything.
- Zi Su.  - Older brother Bai Ze.
Although A Ji Ya didn't get hurt, she still got surrounded by fire and smoke in there for quite some time.
Weren't you learning medicine by yourself? You should look at A Ji Ya.
First, I have known medicine since the beginning. I didn't learn it.
Second, A Ji Ya, A Ji Ya. You guys only think about A Ji Ya!
I don't want to talk to you guys anymore.
Her 'Princess illness' has attacked again.
Let's go deal with the Magic Stars.
A Ji Ya, eat your noodles her in peace. Let's go.
- Hey, you guys should wait for me. Wait for me to go together!  - Let's go.
- Let me tell you...  - Older brother Bai Ze!
Magic Stars?
- Older bro Fei.  -Mhm?
What did you use last time to be able to see the position of the magic stars from the Stars Chart?
I used...
I used my eyes. What else could I use?
How could you even see with your eyes?
This is a Hanyu Code passed on from ancient times.
It is one of the world's hardest code to crack.
These random lines have at least 10,000 ways of combination.
Such a complicated contraption, and you were able to understand it?
What are you talking about? I don't understand. Bottom line is I looked with my eyes.
You guys don't see it?
Mother...
Who taught you?
No one taught me. I remember that my dad used to play games with me when I was young.
My dad always made me guess with this item.
Soon after, I learned.
That means that you knew such a complicated thing since you were little.
Maybe...you may not understand this...
but you know...it's very simple for me.
Talent, talent.
It's good that at least in our group, someone understands it.
Otherwise, there's no reason to keep it.
Quickly look at what it's trying to say.
Right, right.
- This side?  East...east...east.
- Is it this side? - Northwest?  -Yes...
Yes, north west. Northwest...
- It's very far.  - How far?
The northwest direction?
Before reaching Mount Tornado.
Mount Tornado?
That means that the next Magic Star will be around 500 miles northwest?
Exactly, that's what I think.
They are also looking for the Magic Stars and they have a map?
Since I won't have an opportunity right now to get to the Princess' Magic Star, I should go with them right now.
Why is A Ji Ya being so secretive?
That's right. It is indeed Mount Tornado!
Isn't it really far?
It is a little far.
- Hey, I am hungry. I want noodles. Go make me some.  - Okay.
You also go too, Zhan Xiong Fei. It's faster with two people.
Hurry up. I am starving!
- Me too.  - No, no, no.
Older brother Bai Ze, there is something I need to tell you.
Tell me.
I think that A Ji Ya is not that simple.
Why do you think that?
Her martial arts is superb and you guys didn't see this today,
but when she was chasing Zha Bu Ha and Gu Li, her face was ferocious.
Think about her background. Learning martial arts to protect herself. Is there something wrong with that?
Who is like you. Born in a palace and surrounded by soldiers to protect you.
Additionally, she let the two go. Isn't she pretty nice?
I am not joking with you. I am serious.
Okay, I know you are not joking with me. I will be more careful in the future.
Then why don't we talk about you?
Me? What about me?
Why don't we talk about...
when you are going to return to the palace?
I don't need you to mind my business. Why don't you go mind your A Ji Ya's business?
Sir, I don't understand. Since we already Bai Ze's whereabouts,
shouldn't we just send a few people to teach him a lesson and this will be done with?
Hiring this person now, isn't that dragging in too many people into this?
Moreover, this person is too expensive and has already stopped doing it for so many years.
You have a pig's brain. If we send our own people,
isn't it obvious that we are breaking our relationship with the Emperor?
Right now, the Emperor sent him to Yanjiao Town
is because of the Magic Star. Our actions this time,
must be done perfectly.
Sir Ding, the person you are looking for is here.
Qian Yi Shou
It was very difficult to get you out of retirement. Welcome.
Let's skip the small talk. I have a way of doing things.
Receiving money and getting rid of the person you want to be rid of
and receive what I am supposed to receive.
Look at his confidence.
You are definitely different from the others.
No wonder you are known in Jianghu as the Top Mercenary Qian Yi Shou.
You are really that Qian Yi Shou?
What? Do you want to try me?
Jianghu number one is indeed not just a hoax.
Okay, what is my deposit?
F..follow me.
I knew that this day was coming.
You are like your dad a lot of the time.
Don't worry. Our fathers will protect us from heaven.
You two idiots, listen to me.
When you are not at home, take care of yourself well.
Don't worry, Thirteenth Older Sis.
Once we get all the Magic Stars and receive money, we will make your wish come true.
We'll let you open inns around the whole country.
Bai Ze, you'll have to help us.
Of course.
Opening one is tiring enough. If I open inns around the country,
do you want to tire me to death?
I only have one requirement of you two.
You better come back as a whole person.
We know.
Thirteenth Older Sis, we'll leave A Ji Ya in your care.
Don't worry.
I want to go with you guys.
I disagree!
A Ji Ya, there will be many hardships along the way. Are you afraid?
I'm not afraid. You are my best friends in the whole world. I want to be with you.
Alright.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Magic Stars Team @ Viki
I said I disagree!
Hey, hey, we're close today.
Hey, we are not open today and we are not welcoming people who sell talents.
Leave!
What are you trying to do?
Actually I've come today to find someone.
I'm not sure if you all recognize this.
If I saw correctly, the person in the picture is me.
Yes, Mister Bai is smarter and braver than the others.
Seeing you today, I can tell that it's true.
I'll introduce myself then.
I am Qian Yi Shou.
Our country's most expensive assassin, Qian Yi Shou.
Did you go into retirement?
You are right. That's why you should all be happy.
This is my first job after coming out of retirement.
Since it's like this, you should know how I work.
Hand over the Magic Stars, and I'll give you the most painless death.
Your name is sure weird.
What is one pair of hands and two pairs? You only have two.
Not only do you look weird, but you lack fire in your limbs.
How about this? I'll add some for you.
Little tricks. Stop trying to trick me.
He... he dodged it.
Older Bro Zhan, are you okay?
Zhan Xiong Fei, are you okay?
I will not lay a finger on a woman.
But, don't look for trouble on purpose.
Let them go! Come at me!
Don't worry. I won't do anything to them.
When I kill people, I get money. Such a money losing deal,
I will not do.
But you...
Everyone, close your eyes!
My eyes!
It hurts.
Are you okay?
Run!
Let's go.
It's up front.
Why is there water in this worn-down temple?
It is one of Ma Da Dao's safehouse.
I never thought we would use it first.
Is your arm okay?
The cut was really big. Why is it not there anymore?
It's fine. Since I was young, my wounds heal immediately.
Where is Thirteenth Older Sis?
Crap, she must not have been able to run out.
- I need to find her. -Hey!
- You can't go!  - I have to save Thirteenth Older Sis.
If you go now, not only can you not save her, we will also die!
I said I will go save Thirteenth Older Sis!
Hey, Yuan Shuai! Calm down!
Hey, calm down!
We don't know if Thirteenth Older Sis is alive or not, and you're telling me to calm down?!
If you go back right now, it's useless. You'll only die.
Plus, didn't all this crap happen because of Bai Ze?
You're right. It's all because of me.
I should be held responsible. I'll go.
- You can't go either.
I don't want to hurt everyone because of me.
This started because of me, I should be responsible for it.
Plus, the person who completely has nothing to do with this is you.
You should leave quickly. Don't get into trouble because of me.
Who do you think I am? I can leave,
but I am not someone who leaves because there's trouble.
Plus, I have no home to return to and you are all pretty nice to me.
Stop arguing. So annoying.
I know this place well. I will go check it out first.
Don't follow me.
- Be careful.  - Mind your own business, so nosy.
What is happening?
My mind is going crazy.
When Older Bro Fei returns,
I will go save Thirteenth Older Sis with him. If we can't beat that guy Qian,
then I will bow down to him. Over and over again, until he lets her go.
What riches? We don't want it anymore. What stupid Magic Stars? We don't want that anymore, okay?
Bai Ze, just let us go. I can also bow down to you.
Sorry, this all started because of me. I will apologize.
Sorry.
Hold up.
Sit down.
Give me your foot.
Hold it in.
Don't be scared.
I said that I will not lay a finger on women.
Your ankle was sprained.
If you don't fix it immediately,
Be careful of it leaving any residual problems.
Please safe keep my zither.
I will come back to get it.
Older Bro Fei, how is Thirteenth Older Sis?
She's okay. Let's hurry and go. He will catch up to us soon.
- Why is she okay?  We need to leave now. It is not safe here.
Let's go, let's go. He is already here.
I told you to run earlier. Now it's too late.
Hey, what did you do to Thirteenth Older Sis?
You should think about yourself first.
Besides Bai Ze,
everyone move away.
Say, Bai Ze,
your good luck is coming to an end.
Hold up.
I know I can't escape you anymore today.
But there is one thing I want to ask.
Who wants to kill me?
Is it Ding Song?
How can I tell you that?
According to my rules,
I never reveal who paid me.
Older brother Bai Ze has an emperor's command to fulfill.
You dare to kill the Emperor's men too?
This is not something that I need to worry about.
My mission is to kill him.
I'll keep him busy. You guys leave.
No, I'll go help.
Hey, don't rush it. I have an idea.
What idea? Say it now.
Ma Da Dao designed a defense trap.
I reckon that we still have a chance.
Close you eyes!
You little rascal, using again these scum tricks.
Run!
Run quickly!
Quickly!
Hurry up!
Ma Da Dao?
Tell them to help us!
Hey, Older Brother.
- Look.  - Ma Da Dao!
- Ma Da Dao!!  - Good.
We were looking for them and now they appear without us doing anything.
- If you want to kill Older brother Bai Ze, first kill me.- Zi Su.
Hey, older brother. It looks like they have another person.
Right, even if there was ten more, it would be fine.
Why would be scared of them? We have to get our revenge,
you know?
Princess Zi Su, please move aside.
Hey, older brother, why are they fighting amongst themselves?
- Can't you even tell? He's not with them.  - Oh.
Older brother, what should we do?
We should help Zhan Xiong Fei, what useless things are you saying. Go help.
Go! Go!
Why are so many people looking for trouble today?
Bai Ze, you can live for another moment.
After I get rid of them, let's talk again.
Bai Ze, what kind of person is he?
Wow, oh my god.
Brother Dao, fighting! Brother Dao, fighting!
He's good.
Hey, let him experience our high-end technology.
What is that?
Ready...
You go...
Wow...
Let's go, hurry!
Zhan Xiong Fei.
Do you want to try it too?
Eunuch Fong, Eunuch Fong!
Eunuch Fong!
Emperor, are you okay?
Eunuch Fong, I had a nightmare.
Emperor, what nightmare?
I dreamt that Zi Su
was captured by some people from Tibet.
Anyway, it was a daze.
It totally isn't like a dream.
It's like I am bewitched.
Could it be...that it is Ding Song again?
Right. Preposterous!
I kept enduring him but he is really too much already!
What are you guys doing?!
Do you plan to rebel?
Aren't you going to hurry and kneel to welcome His Majesty?
Master!
- What is it that you are rushing like that?- It's the Emperor.
Emperor suddenly came to our manor.
He will be coming in soon.
Aren't you still going to hurry and welcome him?
Yes.
Greeting, Your Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Today, I came so suddenly. I am not disturbing you, right?
If Your Majesty needs me for anything, you can just call for me to go to the Palace.
Causing you to personally come here, I really am in fear.
Actually, it is also not some big thing.
It's just that last night, I made a dream.
I dreamed of Royal Father.
Royal Father even told me that I should personally visit you like what he did in the past
and try to learn the good principles of governance from Minister Ding.
- This...- And also,
Royal Father also said that Minister Ding's skill to write with both hands
has really reached great heights.
I really want to see it.
This...
You don't plan to not give me this little honor, right?
Since it's like that, then I'll humbly showcase my skills then.
May Emperor look at it.
The purple cloud is coming from the west. (The coming of good fortune)
Good!
It is indeed marvelous.
Su Bing Rui, what really do you want?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Minister, General Su Bing Rui searched our whole manor
without regard for right or wrong.
Emperor, what do you mean by this?
My subject, don't be nervous.
Right now, the whole government and citizens
are spreading rumors that Minister Ding is hiding some precious rare treasures.
That's why today, General Su and I came here to investigate about it well
so we can clear your name.
General Su, how's your search?
Reporting to Your Majesty,
I led a group of men to check Minister Ding's storage room. We didn't find any gold or silver.
There are just a lot of rare treasures.
With Minister Ding's salary, I'm afraid that it's unlikely that you'll able to buy such things for several lifetimes, right?
That's right. I can't afford to buy any of these precious treasure.
Because these treasures are not mine.
Never thought that you'll admit so fast.
We have hard evidences and your testimony. What else do you want to say?
Reporting to Emperor, since we've already found evidences of Ding Song for corruption and abusing the law, why don't we arrest him now?
Arrest him!
Wait. Reporting to Emperor, I have something to say.
Your Highness, General Su, please listen too.
I can tell you where these rare treasures come from.
These treasures were all granted to me by the past Emperor.
If you don't believe me, you can check it from the records of the Internal Palace Affairs Bureau.
It is very clearly recorded there.
My beloved subject, don't misunderstand. Of course, I believe you.
That's why the purpose of this action today is to stop the rumors outside.
Enough already. Now that the truth is told,
it's also as I expected, that Minister Ding is innocent.
Your Highness, this...
Spread my edict! Starting today, both inside and outside the Palace,
if anyone should tell lies again about Minister Ding's matter,
all would be slapped 20 times with planks!
Yes.
- Let's return to the Palace.- Respectfully sending off Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
You found something already?
No wonder Ding Song is completely confident this time.
This time, he really was saying the truth that those treasures we found
indeed have records in the Internal Palace Affairs Bureau.
Oh?
Looks like...we really went at a wrong time.
We didn't reach our goal and even alarmed the enemy. Ding Song is really hard to deal with.
I was afraid that because General Su was shamed at Ding Song's manor
and given that he has such violent personality,
what if he wasn't able to endure it
and directly clash with Ding Song?
Eunuch Cao, no need to worry about that.
For grand matters, General Su still know how to behave.
Then...towards Ding Song...
Let's not make rash move for now.
Let's wait for news before deciding on our next step.
I still have one person. It's time for him to make an appearance.
Ding Manor
Minister, the Doctor is here.
Qian Meng
- Minister Ding.- Sit.
Minister Ding, did you judiciously took the medicinal soup I prescribed you?
I have always been.
Then how do you feel about the effect?
Very good. My headaches doesn't attack anymore recently.
Minister Ding, your pulse is a little chaotic.
There are signs of weak liver and kidneys.
May I ask if you have been excessively tiring yourself recently?
For the Emperor and the society, how can I work hard?
It's just that recently, the Emperor seemed to have some opinions about me.
But everyone can see my loyalty.
Is that really your sincere words?
Purple Cloud Coming from the East
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, Doctor Qian Meng is here.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Okay. Rise. Eunuch Cao, you all leave first.
Yes.
Qian Meng, is there any abnormal actions form Ding Song?
He was very careful. Speaking about his loyalty while ranting about his hard work.
As for others, he refuse to say even a word about it.
But did he take the medicines you gave him?
He said that he did but in reality, I know that he never too any.
And also...his headache is very weird.
I can't find any disease or cause.
Okay. I know already.
Qian Meng, you did well.
From now on, you must continue doing medical check-ups on Ding Song
and then come here anytime to report the situation.
As long as it is Your Majesty order,
I will surely do my best to do it.
Okay.
Magic Star, please grant me power.
Even if it is only for six hours,
it can already let me use the Invisibility Technique to eliminate him.
Let's go.
Everyone, stay here. Eunuch Cao, please come with me.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, look here.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Magic Stars Team @ Viki
Ding Song?
Your Majesty, the black magic star is indeed here.
Ding Song, what excuse can you still say now?!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
hurry...somebody come!
Men! Save the Emperor!
Hurry!
Hurry.
Your Majesty, you must hold on.
Hmp! Overestimating one's capability.
This Ding Song is really bullying intolerably. How about we collectively send a complaint?
Sigh. What should we do?
It's wrong to advance or retreat. This...
Why don't we just listen to General Su?
♫ How long can my friends around me to accompany me? ♫
♫ I’m tired of hearing those comforting words. ♫
♫ I’m pulled between courage and collapse repeatedly. ♫
♫ I cry out to myself to hang in there. ♫
♫ I’m still awake at 3 in the early morning. ♫
♫ I can only expect for a good night sleep but not having it. ♫
♫ If I’m not careful, I’ll be disturbed once I think about you. ♫
♫ Memory has been overturned into a kind of sin. ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is wrong but so what. ♫
♫ Loneliness is also just a process. ♫
♫ We still have next person waiting for us. ♫
♫ I’ll remember those wonderful things. ♫
♫ Shedding tears isn’t need. ♫
♫ Thank you for your choosing. ♫
♫ Don’t force myself to give blessing. ♫
♫ Be a mature person. ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is worth the pain and so happy. ♫
♫ I need to learn to let go those I can’t part with. ♫
♫ Having loved one very much is wrong but so what. ♫
♫ Loneliness is also just a process. ♫
♫ We still have next person waiting for us. ♫
♫ With a little regret, I’m more complete. ♫