Subtitle and Translation Provided by:
zuixihuan@lj
Eh?
A dog can born up to 19 pups
19?
Trying to create a fortress?
The need to have some fierce sexual intercourse, right?
Ah...
I want to have sex
and feel that passionate sexual feeling
Pervert
Huh?
Don't start imaging sex just by looking at the dog article
I wasn't
I wasn't doing such thing
When you think about it, people do not welcome these kind of stuff
Obviously
How come these two know exactly what I am thinking?
Huh?
Oh no!
kid bury the glory and the name
Didn't
someone brought this dog to here before?
Here?
I have no memory of it
How about ordering juice?
Welcome
Sae, we have to stay alert since there is always something happening here
You're right but it doesn't bother me
You're right
What's wrong with Asami-san?
I fought with someone and we didn't talk for a week
You're right
saying stuff like "you never understand me"
Probably fought with a man right?
Man?
Fathers are really annoying
Fathers are indeed annoying
Fa...
Father?
So the reason why Asami-san is like this is because she fought with her father
Hey
how can you talk about your father like that
But he's annoying
Exactly
You have to be grateful
so you can't talk like that about your father
Originally you girls came from your father's sperm
That's disgusting
What the....stop talking about it!
Yea
Asami-san
They are finally moving
We have no time
Yes
Making weak-minded people to master their psychic ability is an extremely dangerous task
If he or she has a rotten desire
then there will be no way to continue
First we must put the psychics on the right path
With this we already have the ability to get close to them
We must hurry up and gather them together
Yes
Akiyama-kun
the fate of the world
rest on our hands
I am saying the truth
erotic stuff is a really deep matter
Huh?
What is it?
Isn't
that Natsume sensei and Hayashi sensei?
They are probably having an affair, right?
Both Natsume sensei and Hayashi sensei are not married, right?
Being a teacher and allow to do this
is really erotic!
I just said they are both not marry
The sexual intercourse must be good, right?
Don't be like this Yasu!
Don't be like this!
Yasu
So it's our students
Shit fucking asshole
Don't be like this!
The teachers are having an affair!
Yasu, don't be like this!
Don't be like this, Yasu!
Fuck
Penis!
What's wrong, Yasu?
It hurts!
What's wrong?
Penis!
Penis?
What about it?
Someone is holding on to it
Holding on?
Natsume-kun
look here my own penis isn't feeling comfortable either
This is the best way to punish fucking assholes
Fuck!
Could it be
Natsume sensei...
Hayashi sensei?
both of them...
Politics right now
That's not right
Japan's economic problem is actually very deep-rotted
Nagano-san
Eh?
Do you want to order again?
How do you know my name?
You're
a psychic, right?
Eh?
That...
es...
espresso
you want espresso?
Okay, I got it
so dangerous
finally lost her
This is my first time seeing such big breast
I can't take it any longer
This is the best plan so there shouldn't be a problem
Crap!
How is this possible?
I thought I clearly lost her
What is this, still chasing after me?
Wait!
This is not okay
Go back with me
Wait!
So interesting!
This is so good!
Nice
If it is like this then there will be no problem running away
What is this?
Stop!
This is...
capoeira
Oh!
so it's like this
If you're going to use force then I won't go easy on you
It never occur to me that I have to use this tactic this fast
Upcoming is a special segment of Jackie Chen
Jackie Chen is the strongest
Telekinesis strongest point is striking at stuff
The most handsome man
This is
end of the world winds fist
Huh?
Crap!
How come it only moves her breasts?
But it's so good to look at
Forget it
Oh!
So black
So there was no need for physical strength
Right
This is the perfect time to make my escape
If you can run up to here alive I consider you the winner
How can it be so noisy?
My head is nothing but his matters
How come it is only fill of Yoshiro?
Did I became crazy?
After all, a psychic...
Miyuki-chan
What?
You need to learn how to walk
It's dangerous
Sorry
What was Miyuki-chan doing at first?
How come you were saying my name in your head?
Eh?
Yoshiro and so on
Ah!
So it wasn't unintentionally
but a confession
What did you say?
I never said anything like that
-Then say what it is
-It's nothing!
What's wrong Terumitsu-san?
Where did you fall from?
That hot sexual woman!
Kamogawa Yoshiro!
Hirano Miyuki!
Please come with me!
First please allow me to introduce myself
I am from Tokyo University
specialized in psychic affairs
Asami Takahiro
I may not understand how general people suddenly become psychics in the waking state
but
the psychic abilities that is coming from this small town
we knew the answer from our research done years ago
Therefore
this is all the information we have on psychics
In 19th century
in a small American town located in Minnesota called Dultch
appeared
a lot of psychics like you who transform during your sleep
That is because once every 100 years the celestial bodies are align
and then the bodies would emit rays. The rays emitted point straight at this small town for some time
And now
the alignment of the celestial bodies
is happening again
shooting its rays at Notsu in Oita Prefecture
This happened
during the previous eclipse
So there's
a reason!
However, the rays that is pointing at this small town
doesn't mean everyone can become a psychic
This has to do with the exposure of your cells in your body
There are 3 requirements
Of course
I am in the deity in this matter
So people like us who have this special talent
are psychics who experiences
it during a waking state!
3 requirements
The first one is
never had sexual experience before
Eh?
What kind of requirement is this?
If its like this
we are all virgins
You're still a virgin
Miykui-chan,
that is shocking
What's with your expression?
What's so shocking about it?
Ah
so it's actually common for people to be like that
However, thinking it again that means I am a virgin like you guys?
No wonder my psychic ability trigger by erotic matters can only be awaken during a wakening state
Oh, so it's like this
Hm...
but i don't like how its gregarious
don't blame me for such thought
Next is the second requirement
the next part should be why we are choosen, right?
Then
during he eclipse when the rays are pointing at this small town for a few minutes
This must be how
we are choose by celestial beings
Your body
must be able to reach a high climax state
Huh?
And when people achieve this high climax state
it's calls masturbation!
Correct
Miyuki-chan
So girls also masturbate, Hirano?
Semen deposit confirm
Miyuki-chan
so it's like this
Lastly, the third requirement
You must have an extreme case of inferiority complex
If you satisfied these three requirements you will become a psychic
It's like this?
That's it?
This doesn't have anything to do with being chosen by the celestial beings!
It doesn't matter if you believe it, but I do
However, from the celestial bodies to your power this is the conclusion of our research
Morever, this is Akiyama-kun
like you she fulfills these 3 requirements
and also encountered the eclipse, thus making her a psychic too
If you say it like this
So you masturbate too?
The psychic ability you have during the waking state
is based on your level of consciousness
She was scare of being used as an experiment
like this she receives the power of precognition
semen deposit is coming out
Yes
She always had an inferior complex with her breasts
So whenever someone is staring at her breasts
she would be able to use this ability
That's why during that time
you let me see your breast
At first you were talking about those psychics in America
what happened to them?
Truthfully
this is the reason why we are gather you here
This is an event that happened in 19th century Duluth
The psychics
they were all killed
Killed?
Why?
Yes
The entire group was killed
Everyone with psychics power
eventually killed each other
Killed each other?
Why?
Why would they kill their own kind?
It can't be
right now
the same thing will happen to this place
This was a forum I discovered
2 weeks ago on the Internet
These are the messages left by a suspect
What is this?
You must be joking
He's right
Don't scare people
This...
We need to hurry up and find out
the person who left such messages
The time has finally come
All psychics have a mutual attraction toward one another
Therefore all of you have to be conscious of your surrounding
and when you find something contact me immediately
We cannot let Notsu in Oita Prefecture
become the second Dultch city
I will use my ability
to save the world
I hope everyone is able to lend me your ability
We have to save Notsu, Oita Prefecture
no we have to save the world
or else it will fall in the hands of evil!
The time to save the world has finally come
Is this for real?
It all sounds so silly
Is what he saying even true?
He's saying I am a virgin, that point proved that he is wrong already
That theory was probably a prank, right?
You are a virgin
Wait!
Perhaps
you all think him being a professor
is fake too?!
If he says its the truth then its the truth!
why would a professor lie?
You're right
At a time like this receiving such message
it is difficult to believe it is a prank
However
We have to believe a professor!
Ah
I have to go to work
The schedule at the mahjong house is pretty strict
Oh, I am sorry but I am coming over right now
Ok, I'll be leaving first
The point is
we have to work together now!
If we continue like this we might end up as sacrifices
I need to help my team come up with a plan
pass
bye
Pass
Then bye
I need to
look after the shop so bye
Why?
I am sorry, Yo-chan
This sounds too scary and ridiculous
I can only move erotic stuff
There's no way I can help you
If you two have time, stop by my shop to have a cup of coffee
Then I'll leave first
Crap
What's happening?
What's happening?!
Yoshiro
truthfully
our psychic ability will not be able to help with anything
Bye
Yoshiro
Bye!
So it seem Asami Takahiro
has many psychics at his side!
if we were to gather and summon them
bond together in the name of friendship?
That's impossible
What do you think will happened then?
They definitely will...
Then we'll throw in a confrontation
Just by tripping over a rock
it will destroy everything!
Yoshiro?
Yoshiro
I really do want to help him
How did it turn out like this today?
So Terumitsu-san and the others never wanted to save the world
This is bad if it continues like this
What do I do so Asami-san's dad will accept me
Mail?
What is this?
Asami-san's kidnapped photo
(Attention to all psychics. The girl is in our hand now )
Kidnapped!
Yoshiro-kun
It most possible that it is their doing
It must be the psychics who came here to exterminate other psychics
It seems they have taken notice of us
I'll save her!
Don't act so reckless
We still don't know
anything about them
Yoshiro
Hey!
Yoshiro-kun!
Kidnapped?
It can't be but Sae?!
It seems she been kidnapped
Then we have to hurry up and save her!
But we first have to find someone who can defeat them
But if you say it like this...
We must
protect the world
Miyuki-chan
The voice in your head
I heard it all
Will anyone else come?
I already contacted the professor
I can't reach the others!
If that's the case,
its just us two
who is going to save Asami-san!
Asami-san!
Where are you?!
I am here to save you!
I never could have believe you two are actually psychics!
Hayashi
and you too Natsume
Hayashi sensei
give up now!
Let Asami-san go!
If you two can win against us then we'll discuss it
Perverted sensei!
Super wind!
Such a pretty blow
This is not the time to be having an erection!
Fuck
What's wrong with you?
Penis!
It hurts!
Do you see?
This is our psychic power
I can
create the wind
And Natsume's sensei
can grab onto a guy's penis!
Therefore last time with Yasu's penis, it was Natsume sensei too
Sorry I beat you quickly
This feels so good
So wasteful...
Miyuki-chan!
What are we going to do?
If we continue like this
how we are going to save Asami?
But
we can only hear other people's thoughts
The only thing we can do now is fight with our hands
Yoshiro-kun!
Yo-chan we are here to save you!
Professor!
Everyone!
We are here so you don't have to worry anymore!
Is this a joke!?
Earlier didn't you all said you don't care
We have to work together
to save the world!
How can I possibly say that but then again it's the only way to save Yo-chan,
the only way to get to her breasts
breast milk
hot breast milk
Dutch dairy
You guys can't be save
Let's go!
Team
psychics!
Penis!
Let me have a bite!
I see underwear!
Penis!
This place is?
The kidnappers place
What's going on?
Asami-san!
Kamogawa-kun
It's okay
Don't worry
I am here
to save you!
Asami-san
is fine!
That's good
Sae!
Are you okay?
Father
Professor, you're her father?
I...
How many times did I tell you
you have to be careful when you leave the doors
Sorry
because of my daughter
everyone was put in danger
However, like this too all of you now understands
We are being threaten by a power
that wishes to destroy psychics
In the future we will be face with an even stronger power
who has a lust to make the waking state become evil
Those two are probably
the transfer teachers from their side
I am only a  life guidance teacher
Shut up!
Psychics have a mutual attraction toward each other
That is why
psychics will appears in front of us again
We can't afford to
let what happened to Dultch happen to us!
The true plan starts now!
It isn't a time to run away
I also don't want to see myself get kill
Actually
that was well said
But first we must be able to touch the assistant's breasts before discussing this again, right?
You're right
What do you mean true plan?
psychics?
You are all crazy?
How could such thing exists!
You are all nothing but a group of perverts!
Wandering eyes while jerking off boy!
A prostitute!
The coffee shop pervert!
You're a good-for-nothing shorty!
The world does not need such abnormal perverts!
What are you saying, we saved you!
Don't come over slut!
How could you put me in such a position, and in a ghost town like this?
Tetsuya never contacted me once
The school are full of weird people I don't care about!
All of father's excuses is just his research
Because of all you, my life has turned upside down!
On mother's death bed
because you were absorbed in these stupid psychic matters you didn't come back on time
Actually have you ever though of us as your family?
You are all crazy!
Asami-san
It's almost time
Professor Asami
In this town
the psychic...
What's wrong?
Get lost
What's the matter?
Ah...
You accumulated too much and need to release